
<!-- Entity Name: moqui.entity.document.DataDocumentField sql table: DATA_DOCUMENT_FIELD --><entity entity-name="DataDocumentField" package="moqui.entity.document" use="configuration">
    <field name="dataDocumentId" type="id" is-pk="true"/>
    <field name="fieldSeqId" type="id" is-pk="true"/>
    <field name="fieldPath" type="text-medium">
        <description><![CDATA[String formatted like "RelationshipName:RelationshipName:fieldName" with zero or more relationship names.
            If there is no relationship name the field is on the primary entity. More than one relationship names means
            follow that path of relationships to get to the field.

            This may also contain a Groovy expression using other fields in the current Map/Object in the document by
            the path or any parent Map/Object above it in the document. When an expression is used a fieldNameAlias is required.]]></description></field>
    <field name="fieldNameAlias" type="text-medium">
        <description><![CDATA[Alias to put in document output for field name
            (ie final part of fieldPath only). Defaults to final part of fieldPath. Must be unique within the document
            and can be used in EntityCondition passed into the EntityFacade.findDataDocuments() method.]]></description></field>
    <field name="fieldType" type="text-short">
        <description><![CDATA[The ElasticSearch field type to use, default is based on entity
            field type or for expression fields defaults to 'double'.]]></description></field>
    <field name="sortable" type="text-indicator">
        <description><![CDATA[Indicates the field should be sortable. This is needed because
            in ElasticSearch we have two string types to work with: text (tokenized for search, not sortable) and keyword (sortable
            but not tokenized for search). In ElasticSearch this adds [field name].keyword field of type keyword to sort on if the
            entity field is a 'text' type ElasticSearch field.]]></description></field>
    <field name="defaultDisplay" type="text-indicator">
        <description><![CDATA[Fields displayed by default, set to N to not display in output.]]></description></field>
    <field name="functionName" type="text-short">
        <description><![CDATA[If specific the field is queried with the given function.
            Must be one of the functions available in the view-entity.alias.@function attribute.]]></description></field>
    <field name="sequenceNum" type="number-integer" default="fieldSeqId as int"/>
    <relationship type="one" related="moqui.entity.document.DataDocument"/>
    <field name="lastUpdatedStamp" type="date-time"/>

</entity>